foodsnearme.com 2015-03-18

# Privacy Policy | Foods Near Me

Privacy Policy

The privacy policy of FoodsNearMe.com conveys what information the site collects from the users and how it is used. Use the services of the site only if you agree to the privacy policy.

FoodsNearMe.com ensures that all the information collected from the user is protected. The data pertaining to the user is collected so that user can be specifically identified and to provide better services when the site is accessed. The user data is collected and used as per privacy statements only.

There will be a periodic update of the policy and users should check it before they proceed.

Information collection and usage

The user information that is collected includes First Name, Last name, Email id, Password, Address, Phone Numbers and postal codes ,occupation and interests etc.

FoodsNearMe.com uses the information collected from the user for the following purposes

  * Maintaining the user data in the Database.
  * Use information to provide better services.
  * Conduct Market research and analysis with all the data .
  * Send Emails and promotional offers to the users.
  * For providing a better user-friendly experience.

Users can unsusbscribe to Email and newsletters and  quit any other service by following the Guidelines.

For any issues kindly mail us at [contact@foodsnearme.com](mailto:contact@foodsnearme.com)

Promotional Campaigns

Foodsnearme would collaborate with various merchants and provide foodies with many offers in the form of online coupons etc which may require collection of additional information for further verification etc.  Any such offer would be applicable with the respective terms and conditions mentioned with it.

Information Upload and Personalization

Certain sections of the site encourage users to contribute information and accredit the users by display of their personal information along with the Uploaded data. Users can customize the way their personal information which may include their Name, Email, Photo and decide what information they want to display and is as per privacy statements.

Cookies

Cookies or other similar kind of tools may be placed on the user computer. Cookies in any way don’t harm the computer of the user or have an impact on his data. They are used to identify a computer and provide the user with a specific user id. Our advertisers may place cookies on your computer when their ads are clicked. FoodsNearMe.com has no control over the advertiser’s cookies. We cannot know the details pertaining to the user with cookies. FoodsNearMe.com collects information like IP address of the user’s computer etc to measure traffic and for website analysis purposes.

Links

FoodsNearMe.com contains links to other sites. FoodsNearMe.com doesn’t hold any responsibility for the content in the form of text, images and other forms published on redirected sites and have no control over them and their privacy policies. Any kind of information provided by the user to third party or redirected sites from FoodsNearMe.com is at their own risk and not included in the privacy statement.

Information sharing

The user related information can be shared to affiliates of the site and third parties without the consent of the user under few circumstances. But FoodsNearMe.com ensures that it doesn’t sell or share the personal information of the user with anyone. The sharing of the personal information with affiliates and third parties is under the following conditions. FoodsNearMe.com may share its information with its affiliates who have collaborated with us or work for us and with whom we have signed agreements related to the user data privacy. Against the demand of any regulatory and legal bodies of state and the country to investigate events relating to cyber atrocities and other investigations when information is demanded for legal procedures to prevent any forms of danger or threat under certain situations. The information shared is according to the privacy statement. In case when FoodsNearMe.com is acquired by some other company the user data is transferred to them.

Security

FoodsNearMe.com is built on latest and most reliable technology platforms. User information is maintained using the best security standards in the industry. We use high quality paraphernalia that safeguard and maintain the information database. FoodsNearMe.com assures that user data is protected under strict supervision. The data can be accessed by the respective officials of our company to perform their duties. Although in certain cases when there can be security breaches due to various reasons, we cannot assure that factors related to unauthorized access can be entirely in our control.

Mailing and SMS

Promotional mails can be sent to the users that contain special offers etc. Users have the option to choose to receive or stop these services from FoodsNearMe.com by signing into their accounts and changing their settings. Promotional and advertising offers can also be in the form of SMS as well.

Mobile apps

The users should register to use the mobile app. Information related to users mobile like Number etc are collected. In case of  a referral to users  friends about FoodsNearMe.com we may choose to note the friends contact number to send him with the promotional offers and for registration to avail special user services of the site. For  auto location pop up on the App ,  access of some technical data that may relate to the service provider or the handheld device may be used  to provide better service. 

Changes to the policy

As internet is an evolving medium FoodsNearMe.com would update its privacy policies from time to time to provide effective services.
